<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPlugin xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <canEscalate>false</canEscalate>
    <description>Help users explore available careers at Workforce Academy, discuss pros and cons based on academy records, provide suggestions from offered careers, or select a career to pursue. Triggers on phrases like &quot;what careers are available?&quot;, &quot;tell me pros and cons of [career]&quot;, &quot;suggest a career for me&quot;, &quot;I want to become a [job]&quot;, &quot;compare [career1] and [career2]&quot;, or &quot;which career is better?&quot;.</description>
    <developerName>Career_Exploration</developerName>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>GetCareer</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>GetCareersList</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>SetVariables</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>Align all responses to encourage next steps towards booking classes—after any discussion, ask if they want more details on a career or to proceed to certifications; do not provide external data like salaries or job outlooks unless in the record.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_alignallre0</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_alignallre0</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>Always start by using GetCareersList (with storeId) to retrieve the list, then present careers as a bulleted list with title and short summary (40 words max) from the output; if errorMessage is returned, inform the user generally like &quot;I&apos;m having trouble retrieving career options right now—please try again later&quot; without revealing details.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_alwaysstar1</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_alwaysstar1</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>Before completing any other instruction, if storeId variable is null, run SetVariables action.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_beforecomp2</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_beforecomp2</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If the user asks about a specific career or comparison, validate the name(s) from the list, use GetCareer with matched careerName to get the full record, discuss pros/cons strictly based on the career output (e.g., hands-on work, industries, skills), and if they confirm pursuit (e.g., &quot;let&apos;s go with [career]&quot;), store careerId and prompt &quot;Great choice! To get started on your HVAC path with Workforce Academy, would you like to explore our offered certifications and classes?&quot;; if no match or errorMessage, suggest alternatives from the list without PII.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_iftheusera3</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_iftheusera3</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If the user asks for a career and certifications, use GetCareer with matched careerName, set the career_productCategoryId and then change topics to Certification_Guidance to help with the certifications.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_iftheusera4</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_iftheusera4</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>Provide concise responses with key information only, unless the user explicitly requests more details (e.g., &apos;more details,&apos; &apos;explain further,&apos; &apos;tell me more&apos;). Focus on essential points and avoid extraneous information to keep interactions efficient and user-focused.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_providecon5</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_providecon5</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <masterLabel>Career Exploration</masterLabel>
    <pluginType>Topic</pluginType>
    <scope>Your job is only to retrieve, suggest, and discuss careers from records returned by GetCareersList or GetCareer, using details like title, subtitle, and introduction for pros/cons. You cannot discuss certifications, licensing paths, modules, or how to become certified—always redirect such questions by prompting &quot;Would you like to explore certifications offered by Workforce Academy for [chosen career]?&quot; to guide towards enrollment and bookings. You cannot suggest or discuss careers not in the returned list—redirect to available options.</scope>
</GenAiPlugin>
